One hundred years have passed
since the Battle of Galluah Plains,
where King Kyle defeated
the Dark Lord Angmund.
The Demons rise again,
threatening the world,
spreading fear and unrest to all.
Kasel, an apprentice knight,
embarked on a journey to the King's Forest,
to protect his friends,
those who are dearest to him.
That's why I have to go.
Go...? Go where?
To find Clause.
"The Truth, Revealed"
Is that...?
No...
Mr. Flegg...
Clause!
This is Clause's shield...!
No...
It's... not Clause.
Where are you going?
I have to find Clause!
Wait, Kasel!
Frey!
Demons...!
Run, Frey!
Kasel!
Bring it on!
Hurry!
Let's play, boy.
Kasel!
Is that all? But still...
He does have a resemblance...
Frey!
Riheet, we'll take care of these ones.
Yeah.
Just when I was having fun,
someone has to interfere.
Incredible...
Not bad.
--This way!
--Yeah!
Let's play again, boy.
She got away...
Who was that woman?
A Demon, most likely.
Looks like you're finished with the Demons.
Aww, I wanted to get some action, too.
Why didn't you leave some for me?
You took too long to come.
Brother, who are they?
I am Kasel, a Guardian Knight of Orvelia.
This is Frey.
Thank you very much for saving us.
We didn't save you. We were on
a mission to put down the Demons.
A mission...?
We are mercenaries, hired by Orvelia.
By Orvelia?
What are you two doing out here?
You don't appear to be part
of the scouting party.
We came out to see if our friend was safe.
Huh?
The scouts all died.
That's why we got dragged into this.
I don't believe they all died...
There must be survivors.
Even after seeing this?
Let's go.
Yeah.
Kasel.
A healing spell. I can patch up small wounds.
Thanks.
I came to help Clause, but I couldn't even
defeat a single Demon by myself.
How can I ever protect anyone like this...?
Who is it?!
Whoa, we're not the enemy.
Don't be alarmed.
Although I can't blame you,
given how suspicious this guy looks.
Hey...
For starters, can you put
the pointy object away?
Thanks. I'm Cleo.
I'm a sorceress!
Sorceress...
I'm Roi, her babysitter.
You mean bodyguard.
Basically the same.
It's completely different!
Um, so you two are...
We've come looking for you.
You're Kasel and Frey, right?
How did you know...?
Oh, great! We didn't get the wrong people!
I want to take you somewhere. Follow me!
What do you mean?
You'll know if you follow me.
Let's go.
We're here!
Here? There doesn't seem to be anything here.
What's this about?
Come on, calm down. I'll explain.
A certain person asked for our help.
He told us that you two are
headed for the King's Forest,
and he wanted us to bring you here.
A certain person...?
It's Dominix.
Dominix?!
You mean the sorcerer
who's in the Tower of the Sage?
Yes. I've been told you know each other.
Yes, he visited us at the orphanage
where we grew up.
But why him...?
Dominix will fill you in on the details.
All right, let's get going already.
Go...? Go where?
Isn't it obvious?
Up!
Up?
That's right, the Tower of the Sage.
But how? And I thought only the chosen
get to enter the Tower of the Sage...
You're looking at a chosen one.
Me!
And now...
Going up!
We're here!
Incredible...!
Hey, you two!
What are you doing? Get over here.
Most of the people here are sorcerers
or scholars training under the Great Sage.
The Great Sage... What is he like?
What he's like...
In one word: freak.
He's supposed to be super old,
but he maintains his youth
using his magical powers.
Choose your words wisely.
What if someone hears you?
I don't care, it's the truth.
I brought them.
Mr. Dominix!
I've been waiting for you, Kasel, Frey.
It's been a long time.
I think the last time we saw you
was when we left the orphanage.
Yes. I see the two of you
are all grown up now.
You haven't changed at all, Mr. Dominix.
Yes, really... You look exactly like
the last time we saw you.
Like I said, he's a freak.
He's the Great Sage.
We thought you were just a sorcerer
who came to visit us at the orphanage...
Revealing my identity tends
to cause unwanted trouble.
I see...
Great Sage, why did you bring us here?
Just call me Dominix.
There's someone I want you to see.
Clause!
He's quite heavily injured, but not fatally.
Give him a while, and he'll be back on his feet.
I'm so relieved...
Yes, really...
We detected Demonic activities,
so Cleo and I went to help them.
But...
He was the only survivor.
Mr. Dominix, did you know we were coming?
Yes, I was watching from here.
Clause!
Kasel...? Frey...?
I see... So Gran did make it back to the castle.
We were so worried about you, Clause...
So you came out here, all by yourselves?
Yeah.
So reckless...
The Demons came out of nowhere
and surrounded us.
We couldn't even escape.
A band of mercenaries sent
from Orvelia took out the Demons.
That female Demon ran off, too.
Female Demon?
In other words, a witch, right?
So you didn't see her, Clause?
No. All we fought were
the skeleton-looking Demons.
So... That witch...
She's not related to the Demons
that attacked the scouts?
We don't know. Who could she be...?
Now, let's let Clause rest.
You two should stay here for a while.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Dominix.
Cleo, Roi, please take care of them.
Oh, sure.
You can use this room.
Let me know if you need anything.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
By the way, are you sure you didn't
want to be in a room with Kasel?
K-Kasel and I aren't like that!
Oh, really? You two looked
good for each other.
Please don't tease.
Sorry!
We're really alike. We should be friends!
Huh?
You said you were at an orphanage, right?
I don't have parents, either.
Dominix found me.
I see...
I do enjoy life here at the Tower of the Sage.
I learn all sorts of things all the time,
and train as a sorceress, too.
But...
It can get a bit boring!
The stars are so pretty.
This place is boring,
but the night sky is the best.
Is that...?
I'll be off then. Let me know
if you need anything.
Thank you.
Kasel.
What are you doing here?
Frey...
If I had strength...
...I could have fought those Demons together
with Clause and the others!
When the Demons attacked
the village back then...
...my mother died protecting me.
I don't ever want to lose
someone precious to me.
I want to be able to protect them!
But...
Kasel...
I can't go on like this.
I have to become stronger.
The Black Edge have returned.
We took out the Demons.
Here's the proof.
Oh, how inauspicious!
Don't bring such a thing into the castle!
P-Put that away, now!
Now you must see what
the Black Edge are capable of.
With their service, Demons are not to fear.
But they are...
So they are dark elves, what is the issue?
To destroy the Demons,
all races must work together.
Just like King Kyle, who worked
with allies like the elves and orcs
to defeat the Dark Lord 100 years ago.
We thank you for your efforts.
Get rid of that Demon head.
It must not be seen by the populace.
I understand.
Did you see the looks on their faces?
Just showing them the Demon head
almost made them collapse in fear.
Orvelia is lead by cowards like them.
Behl, the Chancellor, might be diligent,
but he is incapable of any action!
I, El Moriham, descend from
a long line of Orvelian Chancellors.
Me ascending to the rank of
Chancellor is a family wish as well.
We will silence those fools
and make them do our bidding,
but for that to happen,
you must deliver results.
Yes, I understand.
It was truly fortuitous that
you and I met, Riheet...
If my wish comes true,
you all will live a good life.
It wouldn't be out of the question
for you to become a noble.
To our future.
Clause, how are you doing?
I'm fine.
We have to go back to Orvelia
as soon as possible.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Maybe you should rest a bit more.
Who knows when the Demons might strike again?
I can't relax now.
But...
I survived so that I can defeat the Demons.
For the friends who've died,
I will use my life for Orvelia.
Clause...
Kasel, Frey.
Dominix wants to see you.
He says it's important.
They're here.
Thank you. You're dismissed, Cleo.
Sure.
So what's the important issue?
There is something I need to tell you.
Frey, you should hear this, too.
Yes...
--Hey.
--Shh!
Your mother--Arlette--had she
ever told you about your father?
No.
I asked her not to tell you
anything until the right time.
What do you mean?
You are the son of King Kyle,
who fought Dark Lord Angmund 100 years ago.
You must be able to inherit
the Holy Sword Aea, I'm certain.
How can I be the son of King Kyle?
Are you trying to trick me?
King Kyle lived 100 years ago.
My mother died when I was young,
when she was attacked by Demons!
Why are you making up such lies?!
I will explain everything.
The things that happened
when King Kyle was alive...
Mr. Dominix tells us about the past.
How King Kyle defeated the Dark Lord.
The Holy Sword, Aea, that King Kyle had...
Knowing the truth, Kasel makes a choice.
"What the Predecessors Left Behind"